yeah yeah
[music]
you hack Prudential My name is a week
Ago from Beautiful Da Nang city I'm
going Together is from Da Nang
university of economics treatment serum
my school is I have looked many
different not related to self Is A trip
with the love in the first country when I
first started working as insurance and
five Prudential Vietnam is apart Compact
and treatment process the world and
complete customer relations in some you
and defend your experience I hurt me We
created for my fashion and Australia  and
appears in stunning Spinosaurus first
Lee Taemin this person is right to treat
Myself by great tree sinh Viglacera
guests can select Which are very
twenties appurtenant everything about
the best and most powerful providing For
What is your help protect my surviving
parity to explain the solution and
firmly established In My patience is
really hurt me to have Used because
customer Switch actions and tell you
everything and threaten to work will
of requests will lose my best spots
chocolate speaking I love cameras writes a
furnished in speaking in first person
which Used it convenient and experiment
to my work Please  Hello everyone, I'm Anh
Nguyet. Life insurance is really
important  Life insurance is essential in
our lives. Therefore, today I will
share with you the benefits that
life insurance brings. For
young people around 25 to 30 years old, the
first benefit
is saving money and avoiding wasteful spending.
For example, when shopping on Shopee,
you can stop carelessly buying
unnecessary items because you have to put money
into life insurance. The second benefit is
peace of mind during pregnancy. Do you
want to have all the costs related
to hospital rooms and services for mother and baby and
relatives covered? For a woman, this
is the most difficult time. Why not create
good conditions for yourself and your wife? The
good conditions that insurance brings
will be an incredible motivation for us.
That is, financial protection against
risks. According to statistics, currently, on
average, 500,000 new cases of
poverty and 336 deaths from cancer occur every day, and 18
deaths from accidents occur every month, and this rate is
increasing every year. If we didn't
have insurance, we would be in a difficult situation.  Having to withdraw savings,
sell assets, or borrow money for treatment and to
continue living is especially difficult when the breadwinner
faces risks. With life insurance, the whole
family can rest assured with protection up
to 700 million VND.
That billion-VND insurance policy demonstrates
love and responsibility towards our
family. We say we love each other
very, very much, but that love is
only truly expressed through action.
Life insurance is an incredibly
wonderful gift for a husband, wife,
or even a child
in the future. In a few years, it will be an
investment and a retirement plan for old age. What could be
better? Besides protecting
finances, we can
effectively increase our assets and have a
comfortable life without worrying
about financial issues. Because of
these amazing benefits, and as
people say, "It's better to be
10 years ahead of the mark than a minute behind,"
let's get life insurance now!
Thank you everyone!